# Jacob A. Price

Phone: (385)-439-7599 LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/jacob-a-price1

Email: jake7208@gmail.com

### **Summary**

Software development graduate 3 years experience. Experienced in working with server-side technologies such as Node.js, Express, and MongoDB, particularly in developing web applications within a team setting. In previous team development projects, contributed to enhancing web development with the use of frameworks like Node.js and Express, and worked with JSON Web Tokens for authentication purposes. Additionally, currently expanding expertise as a software/web developer by learning C#, and have gained hands-on experience with Svelte and Tailwind frameworks.

### Skills

#### **Technical Skills**

C# • Node.js/Express

 MySQL/MongoDBHTML/CSS

Soft Skills

PHP

Team Work

Problem Solving

Time Management

### Education

• Web Development Certificate, Bridgerland Technical College, Logan, Utah, May 2023

### Work Experience

Communication

• Server, Jc's Diner 03/2021-Current

• Assistant Instructor, Bridgerland Technical College 06/2022

• Busser, Jc's Diner 01/2020-06/2021

• DishWasher, Jc's Diner 08/2020-01/2021

## Community Involvement

- Contributed an effort to assist with Eagle Scout Projects.
- Contributed to helping organize and facilitate local soccer games through reffing.